(Sheldon:)And she would entertain me with stories
about growing up in Oklahoma.
lnteresting woman.
(Sheldon:)You know, she once killed a prairie dog
with a gravy boat.
(Howard:)That's nice.
Whew. Heh.
That's a lot of beIt buckles.
Funny thing is I only have one beIt.
(Howard:)Anyway, I'll let you get started.
(Howard:)Oh, by the way, the little marks
that look like water spots...
...l tend to stand too close
to the urinal, so...
(Howard:)What you're seeing there
is splash-back.
You make sissy on your beIt buckles?
(Sheldon:)Mee-Maw's forks never had that.
(Howard:)Here is a black light to check them.
For your own peace of mind...
...you might not wanna shine that
around the rest of the room.